(In Memory of Nicholas Courtney)
(谨以此纪念Nicholas Courtney)
(即准将的扮演者，于2012年2月辞世)
(Attention all agents.
Incoming message from Grayhound Leader.)
（所有特工请注意。收到来自灰狗队长的信息）
Professor Watkins disappeared.
Watkins 教授失踪了
Last known whereabouts: International Electromatics
已知的最后出现位置: 国际电气自动化公司
run by Managing Director Tobias Vaughn
该公司执行董事为 Tobias Vaughn
(International Electromatics London HQ)
国际电气自动化公司 伦敦总部
(DOCTOR WHO THEME)
Doctor Who 1963
神秘博士(老版)
The Invasion (Whopix fan edit)
赛博人的入侵
（粉丝剪辑版 http://wp.me/p1mHFo-lH ）
To All Agents: PRIORITY ONE ALERT
by Direct Order of A.G.L-S.
通知所有特工: 最高优先级警报，来自 A.G.L-S 的直接命令
Locate and Detain THE DOCTOR,
Repeat - THE DOCTOR
找到并扣留博士。重复 - 博士
Target sited in vicinity of IE building...
目标曾经在 IE 公司大楼附近出现...